Welcome to the Night Crows
My ga is from the city center
issue
Tonight is very special Two sardines in the airway Don't give me I
think it will be done in three languages
Chinese Russian and English Already
cheer
ax then
2 shot
Because now there is actually a special sound cast doing a live show Ah
snakes Oh
Shazo's love speaking mouth promised to do this for money It's
Sharaku
2 It's a
country where Russian is spoken
Pros
Boys
Everyone is special Well there is a
very special group The
cheering squad is Exit Good new addiction
Goal and club is called
wave 2 ee The
heavy rain and club will make a special scripture for us It's
that kind of club
[music]
32 years ago
First year self-performed
ben
Princeton University is in the middle of this
I said
Derby Star was
t say Engine
to books
Well, they started a project to protect Asian scriptures
Go to home
m I've been waiting for 32 years to do it
first oh Tsa personal import loop  The
leader of that projector, who has been protecting it all this time, is Professor John Brady
[applause] He is
now in charge of the camera.
me
2 r n
10 minutes
sent me
They have already collected about 16 million pages of agreements over the past 32 years.
Please take this as a big learning experience
tome
And I think it will actually take many more years to
translate it fanurse 5 Traditionally, it is put -3 The
work involves
first finding these fading books, then digitizing them, then translating them, and then publishing them online. It's a
delicate process, and we have to
translate it.
Standard phrase w
Yae I think his work will take another 150 years. to
twist the bread sheets expedition macho etc. The
leader will have to go on for another 150 years.
1 bread religious water
[applause]
[music]
[applause] But I
think it will take 700 years to translate those books. is the
landlord shrine par 4 yes failure 288 by  Hitting the head, huh?
Now the first book has been released,
fortune telling,
aaah, there are
still
99,900,990 books left to be translated,
staff,
and the Russian team has
added, inc,
Kazakhstan and other countries like Kazakhstan and other countries like Russian,
aaaaaa, Aichi
A-chan, you A-chan, Tin Pan,
tame,
Oyu Bis, and more than 1,000 people have gathered,
me,
donating money to the Kinryu Bancho project, Ashida Jinden,
radio waves and other sounds,
os, I would like to express my gratitude for the work of the nature director
[music] The
director is standing in the middle by the camera, that is the
purpose of this book, this board pro and cast, to do live,
after this group did this gold club,
Mariart,
what is her, Peter, the
man who was there
[applause]
First of all I would like to thank everyone, the costumes are complete,
0, it should be,
now we have a special lesson
[music] There is
one more thing I would like to talk about, Himeji, let's go, the
three superpowers that exist in the world today,
hd version  Of
course the suit is China I want to go there there isn't
[music] Another one is
Russia, all the Russians are two tulle
countries all Jihyun is so happy Oh, so
Idoe-chan ending
Then there are the English shovel countries
And the Chinese countries
[music]
23 now the kids are chan tv
And the Russian
shovel countries Those kinds of people And the English shovel countries Kitty Aaaah What
I'm proud of is in
this room the
first pants ne
And the people watching online
These
7 beach I
like Yui who has done these three groovers
Little
me
Yumikura I'm very good about that I'm happy
[applause]
Aaaah That's right In
this class today we've been
talking about the governor's colors Up above we've been talking about glaciers It's
instinct The
definition of a kennel
When you're furrying, ramen is a concentrated lesson in February in the US faa
Now it's a town floor It's very famous
Good The
meaning of the word is that it's in your
mind and good will and natural
henan
p Sorry  Grace
Tarata If you have
that way of thinking, it will steal the peace of mind of people Candy Eponna
Frame is a good girl
No, this is really a finger spa of a clay person
[music] Ah, right in front of me If there is a
slope in the mind you want, there is no drawing
10 You will be unhappy Hey,
but that is not all
me to me It seems that it will also
harm your health While being
done, the staff is fluffy
Graphense Pity
a I would like to dedicate tonight's talk especially to Russia No Call and everyone at the club
Foreign object
Nagacho t Mr. T's group is
about the Tower Pick of Silent Voice Implementation Ah, it's
red
What is the connection Stomach ache Negative emotions and insomnia Now I would like to talk about the connection between the
two of them Tono From this, it is a complete abolition of dreams Hmm It is attached
to the set of points
g 700 people have gathered together and conquering is a gathering It is a given Hmm We have been talking
about what the problems caused by the Crimson Ones are
Before entering the warehouse, I didn't mention health again.
This negative emotion will
destroy your health too. Mason, chin,
aname, strawberry,
now I'd like to talk about the same night. I
have an hour with the lady, so I'd like to quickly
talk about that.
Nurinu, see, I'm not told, I think
you all already know, but there are a lot of keys inside the body.
In India they are called planners,
in
Japan they are called period, Rupanchouehime, yes, Tibetans
call it theory, zombie virtual,
me, every day,
what is a Self-Defense Force aircraft?
This kid is energy, I challenged with my finger,
me,
different, favorite, no,
Kiba channel is inside the body and flows along the meridians between Chanel, uh, nya, it's not the
same as manufacturer serious, but process 5 newcomer
[music] it may
look the same but it's different.
Chon, middle, p, ground Chan number
3, s, there are 22,000 channels in our bodies, they are meridians, and
energy flows between those 72,000 channels.
What is the very first starting point for the formation of that channel? Well,
from the moment you are still inside your mother's body, the
moment she first conceived you, on the
1st month of the month,
a small channel was formed in you.
That is called the central channel. It is
also called the middle
channel. As you grow, it will be divided into eight parts. This is the heart part of the main picture. As your heart grows, it will be painful, right? That one central channel will differentiate into two channels. There are
three main ones, although they are not the main ones. In the
adult body, you can do it like this. Hold your
finger like this and place it here. It looks like a
nation.
These three points are the starting
points of the channel. This is the central channel. It
ends here.
That color is the
color of the sun. You select thirteen of them and call it that.
One type is used on the right side. A thin
white color.  There is a
channel and this point balance is where it
ends, that meridian
and on the left side, it starts as a tour, it is a
red channel and the number of lines etc. is that
long, the endpoint is here
astand
As far as I'm saying, there is a name like this in the bankruptcy
proceedings It's not finished, skating face In the middle 5th school it is called the middle meridian In old age, ya bar cho mins, now make the main thing A few moments is the pronunciation of the streak book It is the
color of the day, so to speak Yes, you read 13 lines and say it That is on the far right
side is it is called
Para duty-free girl went 2-way There is To
pronounce it correctly you have to
turn the cedar Try it and go Yeah, it went
If you can turn the bottom well, it will be a
sharp image of an Indian throughout the village
Bach
in That is what you have to do to pronounce the prefecture
liam Three women of Ness 32 chance and land and in
Southcrete n
Miso mixed in It seems like an
injection or something
Sang her  2. How do you pronounce "sheep"? It's
always white, isn't it? It
's a channel for doing things like that, it's called
pink, please. Apples
mean red, and the
English word "pink" comes from that word.
Imai Minamito Salmon, now jumping off February, the exchange is done
on the Chihara Line. There
are 72,000 channels throughout our bodies,
these three are the three most important.
Thanks to Nacha-san for growing up, and
Chan, does
middle school start from here? It's
consistent.
Opening this car,
also a pillar of news patient policy, it opens like this. That was it.
Starting electrical materials, dinner Shin Hyun-ju, the shape is like this. No matter what, it's because that's the reason why
Indian women put red there when they get married. A little island,
San'in Expressway, dark sheets, 4 lines, can be moved with a touch, but carefully
[music] The
floor, that channel is Sherpa,
diagram, bone hole,
apologize to, and starts from below, and that
thing flows along Uraga Bay of the remains
And it flows down to the
back of your throat, the
young lady, the old shop,
5+2,
think, nsr, spa, the way,
and the seats, it
follows the shape of the double, all of it, it stretches out, maybe around
8 millimeters,
bought as the pelvis, but to the
realm of common sense, there is a taste of death, mother Hermy Turbo 1,
forehead 3, star king, February, it doesn't
stop and stretches down to the manga museum on both feet,
and when it comes to the feet it divides into two,
and stretches down along both feet, yes, it's
interesting, it's
better to be stylish,
moon,
the only thing is if the key is smooth and you can make a joke like that, you
say, you are relaxed
and you are happy and you are intelligent,
you will be yokan pilgrimage, mountain lodge Asia, then Songmin,
and on the right is the sun,
once inside, Shin-
chan,
possible, p 5 e 0 ca 4 e, the
sheep Imai Sandai, but
here you remember it like this,
yesYeah
Kurose Sutte
Combat-chan
One center channel
course Wavelength Chodirao noticeable
To the city
Protect Suchon Inoue 13:00 Here
Booth
Eve And the left channel is
2 That's right
ea Arthur
Similarly, we will cross from here In front of the place It's
okay Wits
Now hey
Left and right are close
to each other and there is a check on Settsu store
And we will close once more above the head
Civic station sick room store
And we will cross once more at the castle of the neck God of crime prevention It will be
quick when you go home Hey
And we will come to the back of the heart and cross three times there on the back of the heart
God of wealth San Juan To the
mouth
And behind the belly button Now sorry when we zip Ah
This local version of Earth-chan is cold We will
cross once more running parallel and one more step between the spine
Universal c Number At
pen forum agent
Town The
kids that are there And Pino The
tailbone also hurts  :
Impross,
cross again between your feet, I love you, I have a
pill at home or a project,
one place, all charts, sweet left and right pulses, keep the center channel closed, if you
go and do it too much, the energy will not go well between the middle pulses, before the district court,
how about that,
if all your keys go into the middle pulses you will be happier, wiser and
healthier, sergeant broadcaster,
but if the movement of the machine is crossed into the middle like this
you will not be so happy, not so wise and not so healthy,
2 trillion yen, main city,
waiting for the dream of Windham fans,
one push hero,
yuzu, but if you add pressure to the Ru here it will get
even tighter,
uh
ppk a 6, that's
why when a person is awake they make this face,
success is making them tense, it's the
voice,
esfg, when you all make this face, sigh,
this no fan goes down two levels,
right?
And let's go down these two Japanese pulses too, this way the
rock here will get tighter
At first the juices will be cloudy, then you'll have an
unhappy face
[music] It won't be the
dumbest feet,
look, let's
relax these two, the
rock will relax, the
center channel will start to move smoothly between you,
watch stars
Such people will be healthier, your sister will
become smarter, in
order to make a profit by releasing the log, right? If you smile, the energy will
start to move more smoothly, and it will be fine, I
think,
then you'll be healthier
[music] It's very
easy to plant and increase the higher wisdom of the prefecture,
overcome the earpiece, inch d-stage
panda
token progresses and becomes tea,
Wilshire
smart, just smile,
me,
then you'll be happier and more than
20, you can get Nanachi's crossing
point, there is one, ahhhhhhhhhhhhh,
just two or three,
excuse me
4th and 5th,
6th and 7th, kyun There are
7 crossing points When you
reach those points, the energy will not move smoothly
This is the center channel
Between the center channels, the energy is blocked by other pulses It is
blocked like this
13 genres like this
This is the line center channel
This is the left channel In
front of the hall
2 super king
4 closing the passage of the center channel If you
reach it, the energy will not go well and you will not be able to go anywhere
Now, if you meditate, this channel will split into 2 2 minutes Look
here it will become Japan
Yu-chan
Then the new channel will become monotonous
Solution will not come
Now in this direction this direction this direction here story rain sugar is
character panther just Pan-chan a little fashion part electrolyte usd Yu if
you can see from the end powder dependent version
[music] If you
look down from above
Part of the pattern
looks like the wheel of a motorcycle Like the wheel of a bicycle And
each extra pulse extends from that point
If you look into a person's head like that
me myself  It looks like the
wheel of a witch train
Cho 8
Sensei
Sunscreen 4 naa 9 before it was a wheel
The meaning of the tea master is pronounced chakra
Thank you In
yoga, we are always taught that there are seven chakras, but in April, the
second
san
painted it The
yoga teacher always writes about chakras in beautiful colors, but
gave it a special name, Western but Winds Book Ah Book Chakras are
very wonderful Ahhhhhhhhhh
Chakras are not good
Cherry blossoms are like
this
Stopping in various places Stopping the ten meridians When
you were born Even with the
minsar pattern, when you
are still inside the naogasa
What is a magazine It is already
t Deonchan 2 No There is already a place where they are
bound together There are
two here
Onii-kei I mean, if it becomes cancerous it is not there
Collection
of cheese Because
that tree is really blocked It feels good You
can't go anywhere anymore What is a 1 meter decoction? What is the event
text This blocked Basho is
based on the town name of the town's Pancho detection
First of all, normally,
each dam is a dummy, but when was the very first main one made? It was when you were in your mother's
womb, in the
free market, a few months before you've even been born, wow, the best in
Japan is this bone, so when did the
goddess say this bone was made in your mother's womb, it was
formed between the points,
and the points at the back form the spine, the
three crosses in the suspicious place in JoJo 3,
Yu-chan, that sister's bones are
formed, 2 and there are three points at the bottom, ah, 4 e Ahh  The
bones around the pelvis are the heaviest part, and it's
recommended to start building your body and foundation from the time you're in your mother's womb. It's
formed from the point where the toy tax is crossed. Next, a new one. Wow,
if you all have bones, you should
know.
If you all protect your skin and body, you should
know. And yes,
good moves are useless. Phone, tongue, sign
stand, you don't have bones.
Japanese people don't have belly buttons either.
Window,
moose is said to be the body inside at 2 o'clock.
And there's no barless mail.
Their bodies are molded by light and made by light.
I don't take it and I don't tell doctors either.
Saazun
This bone and skin are different, sooooo good.
Profit 6
f Quark magic 13 is fur.
Small domestic beef 13 is the place that produces the result.
This is very badly designed. The day will come when you will die.
Why do we
get skin and bones from inside our mother's womb? Fu-chan,
who made this knot point of cloth?
6 I said there are three main channels It's not that it's not the Starbucks
channel I call it that The
judge stands up It's Starbucks It's called the Starbucks channel I wonder
why Singer Fighting
Starbucks Star It's not that It's
called that I guess
[music] Have you
seen me in class this week?
Taimei-chan is just breaking the big race Is there
anyone who wants to see me?
To the sea It's not that it's not the Starbucks I wonder
why There are
two things I like The
first is good
I like translating ancient texts
This person I like music The
second is good
8 you do
Washai arrows
I like donuts
free Those two things I like
This is true
4 Coffee and donuts
san
That's my favorite
[music]
When you're doing 4 birds I'm translating this book
Roger Neighboring Girl Band 1
And I'm
eating coffee and donuts A
thin paper buff like Hayama editing the road There's
no way to connect to it
Oh, the person who cooks for me is free to do as they please,
advance tickets,
my favorite days are over, I do
well with Masashi, the
doghouse is nice, I'll
explain my favorite place,
me,
here, Sukesan, maybe someday, with some unwanted
hair and blues, yeah, oh,
how to, Matsue, I'm going to die, a little Nobunaga's fur, then a
vacation to the psychiatrist, lol,
why would I go to that shop, because they
have coffee and donuts, Kamenyoni,
working on the room sinking,
oha, if I go
there I can translate a thin plate
[music], it's
raining, but I'll go there early from the woman, I've cleared my
computer,
and I
order coffee and donuts,
webmoney, eggplant,
then I can translate well, it means the
energy is flowing well through the pathways, I'm
relaxed, oh, I'm going,
goo,
and then,
aaaaaaaa, in about
an hour I'll be on YouTube
[music],
the voice is, I can
go tomorrow,
2,
you  If one coffee and a donut worked this well for translation, I wondered what would happen if I
took two. So,
someone else...
Yoshibear Daym Nyafunya Cafe venue, what's with the lighting?
Listen, earrings. When you're
eating the first coffee and donut, the
energy goes through the middle path, and the
translation works very well.
3 Meldis ane.
This middle path is in place of cognitive ability. Hmm. The
ground level is between the chest of drawers, but... But,
thinking about the second donut...
c loop 2nd floor 3.
All the energy goes through this path under the right eye, and
gathers there.
8 Ah, question. The sea is a
character that's ranked high.
0 CO2. If the
energy gathers there, it's in
front of the house, right?
Playful Crusher Mulberry
Wheel.
You'll have a special player.
The wording is also film-like.
Pop is probably an introduction to the night. You'll start to feel like you want
more.
tasker.
However, weapon Gau.
Actually, is it a woman?
2022nd place 3rd place. Ah, hello
Khan.
First of all, there isn't.  Because it was
carried, a
white path has been created there, that is the clay. It makes me
feel like it is the thinnest at the bottom.
The prosecutor's office is going to set up an account, the
same team is coming out, worrying about it.
Energy can never gather in just one path.
Up c
2 If the
fried onions gather in the path at the bottom right, then there will be no energy in the middle. Uh, the car shop in the housing complex, the
long cup of the inventor is 20 years old, that's not good,
stop.
So I stopped translating. I went to
town easily, "Please give me
another coffee,"
and "Please give me another donut,"
cancel, building a wall. When that happens, I start asking more and more
questions about the translation. This is the
ranking of books.
What will he be like now? Is it
okay? Ah, I get
nervous, I get tense, it gets
heavy. I'm
still working,
but I get very nervous. I'm nervous.
re, carpet carpet, wow, too much
sugar. I've been
waiting.
Then, that's right, what is the
car,
dining room, don't you want another
one?  I
thought I'd like another donut Repairing it at
Curves, rapper's Lil detection and cats
Booth bar alcohol In
other countries too, if I say it simply,
new How to spend time, like
summer and coffee, please ask
[music] Ah, no matter
which country I go to today, the
people working there, hmm,
for
their own,
Tanto Edge,
everyone is surprised,
one more,
cheerful financial resources for a lifetime, is that
okay, really?
Home,
Char,
yes, yes, yes, I'll come in,
re
I'm translating a very important book,
Henriyo,
said I need a lot of summer, said I need
three,
three or four coffees, hmm,
this is very important,
Ay2, it's a
very important book that only I can translate,
one more please, understood, and
then at the shop, plaster, a good deal, little by little, like, I
look for donuts in all sorts of places,
now, Tojo Line train,
sorry, it's on, ah, they
said the donuts are all gone
[music]
co2
web
All the energy was now flowing to the assets of the woman on the left.
4th place When
the energy gathers there,
eo
touch this a
That's the pathway of anger. Oishi
Sturm push modified ah
Spa studies honestly
[music]
Boober
All the energy has gathered in that pathway of anger.
wh A
core has emerged in the body, Tsukazan Small Justice Party free
59 When the energy
gathers there,
anger is there
our Lupin And I thought that would happen, it will get tougher,
Shock
That intellectual squeeze will
stop even mild cases,
pham
f 2 The
quality of the Japanese translation will also drop even further, it seems to be for a long time, Far
Sanpei Classic US-China, let's do it 31 times each during treatment, please enjoy, the
vibration is ah ah Do you understand?
These kinds of emotions are negative, it's a
complete victory,
ugg Rain Latimer emotions will
stop them now, it will stand up, the scent will rise,
and it will also harm your health,
Kiyose Mamoru Quick Dry Try l The logo is a person, something tone-deaf  When
you want to control your anger, you can
heal it and it will be created, and then you will be able to control that desire as well. Then the
energy will
flow smoothly and you will become
more intelligent than before.
Good
and
[music]
and you will become even healthier. Every time you get
sick in your life, it means that one of
two channels is blocked. You just need to let the
wood flow down the middle path. I
knew that,
yeah. If you don't let it
flow at home, you will rarely get sick. If you let
the cartoonist's path flow, you will rarely get sick. Try twisting your body and monitoring the operation. If there are six people, come on, Flets. Try twisting your body and it will open up
inside your body. Wow, the excess is a voice. This is where the
intersections open up and open up inside your body. Ask me and the energy will start to move. Up and it's very possible. Like this, if you stretch your body, the pathways will open up. The
energy will flow as fire and wood, and you will become happier and more intelligent. That's why
we do yoga. Not just for the
purpose of building a strong body, but also for the purpose of improving
your mind.
If you don't do yoga, you'll end up following the robot
and
coming home
[music] you go
into the kitchen and
ask your husband for a hug and then the
securities are number 4 and the news your
husband tells you you're stupid and you
speed through the hotel and your mind is on the
white key if you do not do it then you
can see the chin dance the left channel opens up and anger comes out and the central pathway closes and the machine stops flowing through the middle
OK
that person forgets the sky and forgets the concept of the sky
mind and body when a
person who takes a swallow's nest photo gets caught up in the middle the
body can no longer remember the sky
very interesting when
you get caught up in the
winny and lose pypion before the
notebook Chien before the
pen you know it's
stupid
but stupid people can no longer remember the pen you know it's stupid the
most fashionable house
Kyon house
songs and people and the body and carriers
Tokyo 2 the
pathways get blocked worldly
desires eat away at your body
yeah
Exercise is like the
grass you compete on, the fur is like a
madman, you
can remember the chassis sky
if you do yoga
today,
twist your body, the
path is a key, you
think of going home
[music]
songs and people,
chain negotiations, the
temple moves, the pippa is different, the honey, give me a
hug,
your husband says you're an idiot,
but you
now, what's up with you, it's fine to be a silly
idiot, going out is
open, the path in the center is open, well, at
that time your mind was,
hey cd, different place,
flowing, it was a
scorching hot day, love,
your husband's path was closed and not open, he
thought you were an idiot,
but m 4
[music]
you did yoga today,
your path is flat body,
button,
body also includes the great star,
good, good, even if your
husband yells that the leaves are something, you keep going, the
first thing you think is, it's
not, erone, ha,
my husband Fender is like that, that's
projected from inside me,
your path was wide open today, yes, well, I
remember  。 English: It's a
case
Ah, last week I remembered that I was talking to my own child So
now I realize that the person in front of me is like this And he realizes that he is something he
created from within We get along and are complete opposites The
tree of the person who did yoga in the head
Mountain
CG has various patterns and items
From now on, the people who learned today will have their
energy flowing very smoothly They will be able to
immediately recall the story of the pen It's
depressing Well, there are
20 minutes left There are
5 bosses and I have a question
for you All of you
here are welcome to ask questions
[music] If it's a
test, it shouldn't be like this
Can those of you participating online also ask questions?
[music]
Next, please prepare I I would like to
tell you one more thing If you keep
smiling, if you keep smiling
Repa Matsuzono Central Car Attention Point
Statistics
[music] Do
n't get angry, don't get angry, don't get angry
Remember the
story of the pen Slowly Well,
this is for us
[music]
Central No The pathway opens slowly and the
energy flows freely
And
[music]  。 English: Well, there is no
knot in this, so there is no place to get
stuck, so there is no
place to gather, so the energy flows away, so you can
put it on or a woman or an elbow, and it will become a
cat, Chushusai, small blade, Tsushida, 6 pieces,
the bones will change to the left, you can signal the
water level or take a picture, cheese Chris says,
young lady drug processing fan meeting manhwa
a product Changchun, fragrant tea coater,
and then you
wish, it will
change into light,
local 4
ev 3 and you will
think
[music]
and you will become a field,
your bones, no, if you
understand that the story is about the side, over and over and over and over again, the
button that was refused by Low, porter Chan, cp
North,
high pressure, water is
changeable,
Izumi, then the bones will change into light,
and then it will become a knitted ball,
this body, Los
me, there is a river, there is
skin,
that means that your life is not infinite, you will
die,
so raise 22 d 4 s vip to
say  The
fact that the bones are here means that
we must die
Delusional delusional rats That's right,
this is a business scheme, so
open this channel
[music] Don't get
angry at your master Let's
open the way Even if
your master says you're stupid Maybe I'm stupid I'll do it,
but I'm not that stupid I don't get that
angry
Time divine tools Well, I've been
studying the Diamond Sutra from my subordinates, so I do
n't get angry because it's advantageous I have
bones that are in the Mu 8 Librize
[music] If you are
born, it seems that
people whose ridges have turned into light do not die
Congratulations 4 s 1
People with bodies of light can fly anywhere in
the world without even getting on an airplane
In the future, major fetish direct sales inventory wish Genciter yukata protection girl with Gyuwar You
can even help 100 people at once Yes, it's the first
2 minutes, okay?
Tonachan So please do
n't give your master the main road if it's pure
Stop the ringtone cheese bad  It's a
spring, take the bone of light and swing it and get into the body,
and then it will stand up and the
wood will flow smoothly.
Finally, I'll take
questions.
Chewed,
hmm, gbs, gliding sand.
In Buddhism there is a special third, and we've already gone through the
second, but when we were at the waterfall I wanted to show you the third,
the mood, it's called Ramudra,
22nd
flute, right?
me, ne,
pu, so I
say new hair, jan. This is a really famous one. There is another one, ame, we've been doing it until the year banane. Are you sure? It's true, really true. Below is one called Passlasher, try practicing it everyone,
eggplant,
ahaha,
scene,
first victory.
All the chains are dad, and
then the channels will open up,
everyone will become the button.
[music]
max. Every morning, when you
wake up and you don't feel happy, if you feel depressed, Rush a,
fight, cho, aa
When you look at photos or pictures of the club members, you've probably never
seen them looking angry, but there's always a slight smile on their faces. We'll be
climbing for another 10 minutes, so we'd like to take questions. We'd also like to
take questions from the original members.
tse
d No. 3
Wow, and you, representing the people of Russia, ask a question.
Sapporo City, Atsubetsu Ward Wow, it's a godsend
2 Wow, the
people who have done it are like that
Employee a 4 saying something like that, but they can be
distinguished e Telepost
gapper 2
Party girl to bed
Oh, it's falling dc 4 It's going to be a killer pitcher,
could you explain a little bit about the experience of looking directly at the sky?
[Applause]
Good
[Music]
meant The
best thing is to see the sky directly, a You have to do
five or four or five things First, you have to
have the teacher
slowly
Jack Mickey  Observe and look at
many teachers
11 a
Prebindi Plus Game Passport Article
c 4 Research teachers carefully Choose
carefully And
help teachers I spent
30 years living in the same room as my teacher I was with my
teacher all day long If it was
monotonous, it wasn't No,
if you think you're my student
Witz next week, right? wren
me go If you
belong to a Russian goal or club
Published It's
intense
You're helping Asia today
Baseball field fabric day Lots of
money in this form Ah
me You've been
supporting me in this form, right?
That's the first thing you have to do It's the
most important thing
Find a teacher
Research carefully
All 88 mornings
Sewing in
Then I decide My teacher is my teacher and I ask him if I can be your teacher
Then I help that teacher I
support him The second thing is to
meditate every day - private car
uno
Service department media Hmm The only time you can
directly see and experience the way is when you close your eyes while wandering In the middle of true
feelings んあぁ
Hmm, there are 9 kinds of water jc
learning governor I'm happy to
open a learning session cm
and learning is good
every day
Also laser By the way,
this is the Russian version of my book It's
beautiful even with human kindness and days
This is one set
Thank you for translating everything Barrier
[Applause]
Find the teacher I'm looking at it
so
Stalin and to study study study study
Collect And
finally to the
room I have the
set minutes
Helping the elderly every day and helping those who get sick every day En-chan is the master of the trade That's right
Shopping
Manufacturer
If you want an empty cake so staff position
Ronnie 2 books diagnostic department lie
Resh b is this chief ep bread Is the
place okay
e and then No, I'd
say if you do yoga
Cha
every day
[Music] It gets
faster amazing wow
Speaking of summer
Actually I do yoga every day You may not be able to see it but I do it in
my room so
[Music] That's
because my yoga is much harder than what you all do
Everyone's yoga classes are too gentle, so I
hope the
next question is from the final 8.
I played and I'm not natural, there are
various kinds of vinegar.
One question has come in from online, is that okay?
Karate 4.5 is a
question from a Gold Club member.
Ah
oh daddy fbg Approach 9th place, Barry's and hydration are manufacturers more
February
res forever mine Moose
Noveno ever Pen Good Wife 2
r 1 pro 3 camp cap
ran tp 4
Blind people cannot see pain, but how can you explain 10 stories to a blind person in that way?
30 weeks Champion Club trench
Group f
Good question
[Music] I
like how Chinese people are treated,
Larsson p Power and
Russians also get too deep.
Group
3 For me, yes,
normal type st and 4
Good, I'm very in the top ranks, they're
very fun.
Chain
Naruse's announcement I
like going to China and Russia. I went
to Russia last month, yes
Because I like deep conversations
Make it a thousand processes Blind
people are a very good example It must have been amazing
Ito
see to see
They cannot have the seed to see
Mental b Zoom hard Showmin Kameyo Anchin and common
Wedding
Soon in past lives it was a five-star cancellation
hs 2 It's
decided I was
blessed with the chance to help a blind person but the
leader was Ume
But the Curry guys were too busy Hmm Achievement So they do
n't have that kind of seed They don't have the seed to
see salt
But it is possible to teach them the story of dogs That is, when
humans touch this object they think it is the same when they touch it
Details etc.
Their seed gives them the chance to touch a pen when they are tired of blogging etc.
Hmm When a dog touches this object it is
fun isn't it? Fingers So even if they don't have
eyes or don't have eyes, it
feels like a toy to them
So it can be taught to blind people It's a
luxurious day It's
easy, no problem
Hey, bar
personality examination
ana
The number is after they learn the story of seeds So the
master is in pain area
Seasar 2 is the
first room that people with visual impairments come out of on the course
After the tee is over, the main symptoms are what you have
What is the seed to be able to smoke
Mouton slip-ons Oh, my um, Oga-san, the
authors are the
governor Let's talk about your mother-in-law now
When I visited her house in the 3rd trend, God
Fashion p or Adapter
Disease guidance management type product manufacturer They call me
Michael in that place, they don't call me Michael
Tenmae new service
She is 94 years old and it is more likely that she will hit now If
Sato Nagai pushes the ground microphone
Tenmaya now lol Well, I can
go now and I would like to go with you Cho Becker's
bag is 3 pieces per parking space Well, that is
And I will ask a series of questions Mom, you started Easter yoga I have
n't immigrated So, does that
mean that it's not like Ooi 3- is starting now
I have been there for 20 years so it's
not starting now I have been there for
30 years and that is my health Imizu  Well, I
heard the sound of you moving and starting yoga
4 people along, well,
rev
4 b 6 e Did
n't you teach me the very first class 30 years ago?
Oh, I've been doing turn surfing with Mr. Cho, let's do a
test
Since then, I haven't stopped
1 along all kinds Well, I'm
worried about the art of yoga
5.0 previous thread
After yoga class, I always say I go to a club for the blind Well, it's tough to keep going properly
Angelin,
I'm getting old, you know
My eyes are getting worse at seeing to the side
[music]
Ice Far pu Then of course
I joined a volunteer community college for people who can't see
Because I don't want to lose my mainstay Got it? Aaaaaah If you can get
past it, it's a seed for the blind
Just a little, a
poem you gave me, punch
ok It's an email Inae Temogan Well, the live show ends
here I want to
express my gratitude to New Gold Corrado I'm
really grateful Boo Boo Plant
tension  。 English:
You're helping Jump Brady a lot
Boxing Club
Your Gold Glove is a great idea
50 out of 1002 people on the page
1,500 people running out of the outside of the second part of the city
Studying
Surfing Texts Right There are lots of
rich people too, but they donate more money There are also
people who donate small amounts, but it is measured every month
That is a great help to Jump Brady
Thank you
amaran
[Applause]
Yes I would like to
do Mandala Oh
by Shermie It's Mandala, right Sensei Mmm
Kanocho is the second most important volunteer Jasmine
fn
Good and has gathered lots of participants from the Chinese tube version of
Shibu Dance c Building
[Music]
Yes
Shapement
Cleaner year c
Game ah
d
Sanei Shinrume
yuwa
Tree
[Music]
Zhang Xun Shinra bar show  Iida
nguruzu egg raw
Aman from Kamiya yaka sarcastic
[music]
if you go
dee gyaa goon
sunauna
a 4 to
h version 4 welfare
Panache
2 extension to nara I
thought it was good aa